{
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "Serbia consumes _ times more electricity than the world average per unit of social product.",
            "choices": ["1.5", "2.5", "3.5", "0"],
            "answer": "2.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "_ ordinary 25 W bulbs give together the same amount of light as one 100 W bulb.",
            "choices": ["Four", "Five", "Six", "Seven"],
            "answer": "Six"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ordinary light bulbs last on average up to _ hours.",
            "choices": ["500", "1000", "10 000", "20 000"],
            "answer": "1000"
        },
        {
            "question": "Energy-saving light bulbs last on average up to _ hours.",
            "choices": ["1000", "10 000", "30 000", "100 000"],
            "answer": "10 000"
        },
        {
            "question": "With ordinary light bulbs only _ % of the invested energy is converted to light.",
            "choices": ["2", "5", "10", "20"],
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is best to choose a class _ light bulb.",
            "choices": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "75W of Classic Light Bulb is equal to _W of Saving Light Bulb.",
            "choices": ["9-13", "13-15", "18-25", "30-52"],
            "answer": "18-25"
        },
        {
            "question": "Color light is professionally called _ light",
            "choices": ["rainbow", "energy-saving", "temperature", "smaller"],
            "answer": "temperature"
        },
        {
            "question": "Devices with label ENERGY STAR are in the group of devices with the _ electricity consumption.",
            "choices": ["lowest", "highest"],
            "answer": "lowest"
        },
        {
            "question": "Devices with label AAA is more responsible to use than devices with label A or AA.",
            "choices": ["true", "false"],
            "answer": "true"
        }
    ]
}